What are you doing to Joey?
You misunderstood it.
I have no problem.
Is it true, Joey?
What happened last night?
I blacked out.
Don't you remember
what I said to you?
Even though we are different,
I love you.
What did you say?
So, even what you said to me
last night,
you don't remember?
- You're perfect, handsome.
- Am I handsome?
I don't remember anything.
What did I say?
I've talked to Trigger.
He agreed to what you wanted.
I just want to know.
What if you betray me
like what you did to your best
friend, Major Aglipay?
He betrayed me.
I'm not part of their syndicate.
Hey, what are you doing there?
You're in luck now.
I've already spoken
to my husband
about your husband's case.
When he arrives,
I'll introduce you to him.
An invitation has arrived
from one of our target sponsors.
Confirm my attendance.
I'll try to get access to their
office and find the guest list.
Just make sure that my name
is on that list.
Didn't we already talk
about this, Joey?
You're not coming.
Please, Andrew, I can fight too.
You're so weak.
Okay, I'll beat you.
I got you.
Are you sure?
Joey, can being a black
belter help you here?
Remember, your opponents
are gun smugglers.
It's my hair.
It's always good to be ready.
It's even better if you hit it.
Keep aiming after every shot.
Joey, Joey.
Can we talk?
Are you looking for Peter?
He and Jin Ho have left
to get the guest list.
I wanted to apologize.
Oh, wait...
Are you okay?
Do you have a fever?
No.
Ah...
I thought so, well, you were
going to apologize.
Joey, I'm serious.
I really want to apologize
for lying to you.
I'm not really looking down
on you
because you're a woman,
and I don't think
you're a failure.
I know that, that's why
I don't understand you.
We're all here
because we're helping each other
find Golda,
and you're going
to tell me that.
You know, it's hard to
be vulnerable with you.
You're such a big scammer.
Ah, yes.
I hope you know
that I only did that
because your father asked me
to watch over you.
Father?
Yup...
When I visited him,
I told him about our mission
here,
and he was super worried
about you
because we both know that you
only get more stubborn
when someone is trying
to stop you,
especially if what you're doing
is for him.
There you go.
Well, I wish you had just
said that right away
because I could have taken it
better
than those brutal things
you said.
Okay, I'm sorry, but I only said
that so you can be angry with me
and not think that your father
doesn't trust you.
I understand that.
I'm also sorry
because I lied to you.
I lied that I could do it alone.
But the truth is, I still need
my three musketeers.
I still need you.
I thought it was just me.
When did I say that?
That's why "I thought".
You're assuming.
Hey, compadre!
Oh, it's just a small party.
Yes, you shouldn't miss it, huh?
Yes, yes, it's my birthday,
but we'll still talk business,
okay?
See you there, compadre.
Goodbye.
Hi, Godfather.
Golda.
I have a gift for you.
Oh, you shouldn't have bothered,
but what is it?
Take a look.
Braganza is coming!
Happy birthday, Godfather.
Thank you, Golda.
If he talks sensibly,
we won't have any problems.
Hey, Godfather.
When this deal goes through,
this won't be your best gift.
This will be the biggest
and most bonggacious deal
in the nation!
Bonggacious?
Yeah, bonggacious like you,
like us!
You're such a sweet talker.
I'm so excited for this deal,
Godfather.
I hope it pushes through.
Yes, it will, it will.
Yes, a little, Joey.
As in stressed.
I'm that busy.
Oh, why, Mother?
My boss is taking me to a party,
so I need to finish
what I'm doing first.
Your boss is taking you?
You seem close, Mother.
A little.
I hope so.
You know, Joey,
they're really nice.
Do you know?
Next week, she'll make me
talk to her husband.
Let's see if there's anything
he can do
to help your father's case.
Really?
Oh my, they seem kind, Mother.
How about you Joey,
are you going somewhere?
Joey?
Ah, no, Mother.
I'll see first.
Okay...
Love you, Mother.
Okay.
Do it again.
How?
What's that?
Do you know? We had a lot of
trouble getting that invitation.
That's why we just arrived,
we still had to look
for a target.
Catalina Esperanza.
That would be you.
The theme is The Great Gatsby.
How about that?
I won't wear anything.
We didn't prepare.
Costume?
Wait.
Confirmed, Boss.
Braganza already has a target
here in Luzon.
Who?
Godfather.
They seem to be
planning something.
Alcala?
He's a gun smuggler.
What does Braganza have to do
with him being a drug dealer?
We need to find out what
they're up to, Matias.
There's a party going
on at Godfather's.
It looks like the transaction
will happen there.
Then we need to get in.
Are you talking about
Godfather's 65th birthday bash?
Guess who got an invite.
Don't worry.
I'll take care of it.
Joey, you're taking too long!
Let's go!
Joey!
Coming, wait a minute.
There you go...
There you go,
there you go.
There you go. Almost there.
Isn't it too tight?
Is it okay?
Why? Is it ugly?
Peter, is it ugly?
It's not.
It's just right.
That will do.
Wait, it's hot.
Let me get some water first,
okay?
It's hot.
Sorry.
What's his problem?
Andrew, is it okay, right?
Or is it too tight?
Ah...
Well, I don't know about that,
I don't wear that.
Right?
Anyway...
I'll go outside first.
Oh, it's hard
to talk to them.
Is it ugly?
Jin Ho, it's okay, right?
What?
It's okay, right?
I'm not thinking about you.
Excuse me.
Oh...
Is it ugly?
I don't look like a rice cake.
Oh, Ma'am, the proposal
is ready...
Okay.
The one you asked me to print.
Oh, wait, we can do that later.
Let me look at you.
Wow!
Thank you very much.
Thank you for the costume
you lent me.
You too, you look so elegant.
You know, we should do this
more often.
We should dress up,
and we should go out,
not when it's just someone's
birthday.
Oh, Ma'am, you can do that.
But me, with so much in my head,
and I have to take care
of a lot of things,
I can't do it anymore.
Which is why you deserve
nights like this.
You know, you work hard.
You carry so much.
Even joy needs to be
scheduled sometimes.
Come on. Turn around again,
turn around.
The costume is beautiful.
But it seems like
something is missing.
Is it still not enough?
Well, I'm already shiny.
Come on.
Hold on.
There you go!
Here.
Oh my, Ma'am, don't.
I might lose that.
It's up to you.
That's more suitable for you.
Ma'am, it's up to you.
No. Look at it.
Look at you.
It's up to you.
No, I have a lot
of that in the car.
See?
It fits you perfectly.
Oh my, Miss Yvette...
Thank you.
Because if it weren't for you,
I wouldn't be able
to experience this.
You know, you don't have
to change who you are.
You only have to see yourself
differently sometimes.
Thank you.
Do not cover with your hand
and your bag,
or walk into pitch black.
Then we will lose visuals.
The mic is sensitive.
Keep your hands off it.
And if something goes wrong,
just walk away.
It's okay.
We will still have
footage of the house.
Here's your tactical earpiece.
That's our comms line.
Got it?
You ready?
Yeah.
This is hot.
Well, you wanted that.
You wanted that, remember?
You want to be the one to come.
As for him, he cannot come
because he will be recognized.
I told you I can come with you.
I can be your plus one.
No!
You want to be her plus one?
I'm her best friend.
I will always be her plus one.
And besides, you're Korean.
So what?
Yes, you're the one
going with her, right?
Come on, let's go.
Joey, be careful.
I know you are eager
to talk to Golda,
but if it's dangerous, back off.
The important thing is,
you're safe.
Let's go.
Hi, Louise, Louise.
Good to see you.
Thank you for coming.
- Hello.
- Happy Birthday.
Thank you, thank you.
Thank you.
Ramon, thank you
for coming, huh?
Thank you for coming.
Thank you, thank you, thank you.
Please, please enjoy yourselves,
enjoy yourselves!
Okay.
There are so many
beautiful ladies today.
Oh, Golda.
Long live the king!
Happy birthday, Godfather.
Thank you, thank you, thank you.
Has my gift arrived?
I'll call him, Godfather,
and then I'll update you, okay?
But for now, chill!
It's your birthday after all.
Yes.
Enjoy, okay?
I'll see you later.
Dante...
Yes, Godfather?
Secure all entrances
and exits to this place
when Braganza's group arrives.
My palm is itching again.
I'm not confident.
If he makes trouble tonight,
make sure no one gets out alive.
Copy, Godfather.
Hey!
- Compadre!
- Hello, Compadre!
How are you?
Happy birthday!
Thank you! Thank you for coming!
- Thank you for coming!
- Happy birthday.
Thank you.
I appreciate it.
Hey!
Oh, thank you,
thank you for coming.
Thank you for coming.
Psst, don't smile too much.
Someone might look at you.
You're OA!
Detector.
Psst, don't be loud.
Ah, thank you.
Miss Catalina Esperanza?
Ah, I'm her plus one.
Ah, okay.
You're welcome, plus one.
Thank you. Enjoy the evening.
Thank you.
Wait a minute, Ma'am.
Just SOP.
Sir, don't be loud
because my necklace is fake.
Of course, if it gets lost
inside
and it's real diamonds,
I'll regret it.
So some of the
accessories are fake.
Ah, go ahead.
You can enter now.
Okay.
Thank you.
Joey, I almost had
a heart attack.
Oh my god!
Excuse me, Catalina Esperanza.
Yes, that's me.
Thank God you're here.
The coordinator you were
talking to isn't here.
She just passed on the
instructions about you.
Come with me.
I'll take you to the
performers' area.
What?
Performers?
Let's go.
They have to get out of there
now.
Theresa's here.
Get out of there.
Joey?
Why can't you leave?
This party is so beautiful.
You may not know me,
but I know you very well.
You know, even if I were
the only hope
for Miguel to be released,
I don't want it anymore.
How did someone found out
about our transaction?
You're in my house.
You're not getting
out of here alive.
It's mother!
Get out of the car.
Get out!
Theresa...
I hope your whistleblower
tells you everything.
Who is your source?
We've gotten nothing
out of this mission.
Golda?